altonbrown.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - ALTON BROWN

* * *

**_Brain Food Industries, Inc. – Privacy and Cookie Policy_**

Effective Date:  July 15, 2019

Brain Food Industries, Inc. (“Brain Food,” “we”, “us”, or “our”) is committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy and Cookie Policy (“Policy”) explains how we collect, share, and use the information we receive about our site visitors and the options that are available to you. This Policy applies to www.altonbrown.com and our other online and other web properties, and services that link to or post this Policy (collectively, the “Sites”), or through other means in the course of our relationship with you. This Policy describes the types of information we collect, how we may use that information and with whom we may share it. The Policy also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the personal information. We also tell you how you can reach us to ask us to answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices. By using the Sites, you signify your consent to this Policy. Your use of the Sites and any information you provide through the Sites is subject at all times to this Policy.

Personal Information We Collect  
When you access or use the Sites, we may process and collect the following types of information from you: “Personal Information” is any information that we can reasonably use to identify you. If you are located in the European Economic Area (EEA), Personal Information includes all Personal Data as defined under EEA laws. “Sensitive Personal Information” includes special categories of Personal Information (e.g., racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic data, biometric data, data concerning health, and data concerning a natural person’s sex life or sexual orientation) for which applicable law provides enhanced protections.  Sensitive Personal Identifying Information is defined as information that if lost, compromised, or disclosed could result in substantial harm, embarrassment, inconvenience, or unfairness to an individual.

Table 1.1 describes the Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information that we collect, why we collect it, and our legal basis for processing it.

###### _**Table 1.1**_

**Purpose** | **Examples** | **Legitimate Interest for Collecting and/or Processing**  
---|---|---  
To process requests to receive information and updates regarding Alton Brown | Name, email address, and any other information that you submit through our web form. | The Personal Information collected through the request forms are necessary to contact individuals interested in receiving information and updates.  
  
Cookies and Information We Collect by Automated Means  
When you use the Sites, we and our service partners may collect or retain certain information over time and across different websites when you use the Sites. We and our service providers may collect this information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, log data, tags, and web beacons. Cookies are files that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings in your browser. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please review your web browser’s preferences to learn how to modify your cookie settings. See table 1.2.

###### _**Table 1.2**_

---|---|---|---|---  
  
Please note, however, that without cookies, you may not be able to use or have access to all of the features and services available on our Sites. In conjunction with the gathering of information through cookies, our Web servers may log information such as your operating system type, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. The web server logs also may record information such as the address of the web page that referred you to the Sites and the IP address and actual location of the device you use to connect to the Internet. They may also log information about your interaction with the Sites, such as which pages you visit. Web beacons are snippets of code embedded in webpages and are typically used to monitor activity on a webpage, collect information, or transfer information to servers. We may use third-party web analytics services on our Sites, such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use cookies and web beacons to help us analyze how users use the Sites. The information collected by the cookies and Web beacons will be disclosed to these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Sites. Google Analytics transmits website use data to Google servers.  Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and usage of the Sites.  To find out more about Google Analytics use of data, please visit “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps”, (located at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)) for more information. For information about how Google uses the information, see the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, you may visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. We may combine the information you provide us and information we automatically collect with information from public or third-party sources.

Interest Based Advertising  
This site permits data collection for internet-based advertising.  Brain Food and third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our Sites.  More specifically, our Sites has implemented and used display advertising, and we utilize Google Analytics to implement a specific feature called remarketing.  Remarketing is a feature of Google’s AdWords that allows us to optimize the delivery of ad content specifically targeted to a visitor’s interests based upon previous visits to our site.  Please visit <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2611268> for more information about remarketing lists in Google Analytics. If you do not want to use the remarketing feature from Google, you can disable it by changing the appropriate settings at <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>. There is also a Google Analytics opt-out browser add on that you can download at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

Facebook Lead Ads  
We may occasionally run lead ads on www.facebook.com, and we are committed following Facebook’s Lead Ad Terms https://www.facebook.com/ads/leadgen/tos. Should a Facebook user click one of our ads and choose to submit their data to us (this data may include First Name, Last Name, Email, and Phone Number), the user has willingly and expressively given us the right to contact them via phone and/or email, even if they are subscribed on the Do Not Call List. Participation in these Facebook Lead Ads and the forms generated by them are voluntary and you may choose whether or not to disclose information via this format. If a user submits data to you through one of our Facebook Lead Ads, such data will be governed by this Privacy Policy.  Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained herein, we will not sell Facebook Lead Ad Data under any circumstances.

Additional Uses of the Information We Collect  
In addition to uses otherwise provided herein, we use the information we collect and receive to provide you with services and to operate, maintain, and enhance the Sites. For example:

_To Provide Our Services_. We use the information we collect and receive to provide you with the services or information that you request; to provide you with information about the Sites or required notices; to deliver marketing communications, promotional materials, or advertisements that may be of interest to you; and to customize your experience when using the Sites, among other things.

_To Improve Our Services_. We use the information we collect and receive to improve the Sites, for example by better tailoring content to user needs and preferences, such as by giving you more relevant ads; by generating and analyzing statistics about your use of the Sites.

_To Communicate With You_. We use the information we collect and receive to communicate with you about our Sites and services, to respond to you when you contact us, and to let you know about our policies and terms or provide other notices required by law.  
_To Maintain and Operate Our Sites_. We use the information we collect and receive to protect our rights and to detect, prevent, and respond to fraud; intellectual property infringement; violations of industry standards and our policies and terms; violations of law; or other misuse of the Sites. We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

Sharing of Information  
We may share information we collect or receive in order to provide the products and services that you have requested, when we have your consent, or as otherwise described in this Policy. We may share your information with service providers that perform services on our behalf, such as processing employment applications or delivering marketing communications, promotional materials, or advertisements that may be of interest to you. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. We may share information we collect on the Sites at your request. For example, if you use the Sites to send information to a third party, we may identify you as the sender. We also may disclose information about you to third parties as required by law or regulation and when we have a good faith belief that it is necessary in order to protect the legal rights, safety, and security of Brain Food, our affiliates, our business partners, users of our Sites, to respond to and resolve claims or complaints, to prevent fraud or for risk management purposes, and to comply with or respond to law enforcement or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government or other entity. The Sites may contain third party links. This Policy does not apply to the third party content; you acknowledge and agree that Brain Food is not responsible for the collection and use of your information by such third parties that are not under our control. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third party websites or services.

Do Not Track  
We do not currently support Do Not Track signals but may in the future.  Although we are not a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and do not participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program, you may wish to investigate these programs, which provide an opt-out feature where consumers can choose not to receive targeted advertising from any NAI or DAA affiliate. These links will take you to the [NAI opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and the [DAA opt out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). If you are located in the European Union, you may prefer to use the [EDAA opt out](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

How We Protect Information  
We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. Because no information system can be fully secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

How We Retain Information  
We may retain information that can reasonably identify you for as long as we determine is needed for our reasonable business purposes, including to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

International Visitors  
Brain Food is based in the United States. Regardless of where you use our Sites or provide information to us, the information may be transferred to and maintained on servers located in the United States, which may not provide the same level of protection for your personal information as your home country and may be available to the United States government or its agencies under a lawful order made in the United States. We may also store your information outside of the United States or transfer it to our affiliates and third-party vendors located in other countries for the purposes described herein. By providing any data through the Sites, you hereby expressly consent to such transferring and processing of your data in and to the United States and other countries.

Children’s Information  
The Sites are not directed to, nor knowingly collect information from, children under the age of 13. If you become aware that your child or any child under your care has provided us with information without your consent, please contact us at the contact information listed below.

California Privacy Rights  
If you are a resident of California, you may have the right to request and receive information on any third parties to whom Brain Food has disclosed personal information for marketing purposes within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed. If you would like to make such a request, please contact us at the contact information listed below.

Links to Other Web Sites  
The Sites may provide links to other sites for your convenience and information. These websites may be operated by companies other than Brain Food. Linked websites may have their own privacy policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not operated by us, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of those websites.

Updates to Our Policy  
This Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our information practices or relevant laws. We will post a prominent notice on the Sites to notify you of any significant changes to our Policy and indicate at the top of the notice when it was updated. You should review this Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Sites constitutes your agreement to this Policy.

How to Contact Us  
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us as indicated below. If you are contacting us by email to request that we change or delete personal information that you submitted through the Sites, please be sure to tell us which page or form on the Sites you used to submit your information:

Brain Food Industries, Inc.  
33 Garrison Road, SE,  
Marietta, Georgia 30008
